Open bag
Get onion bag
Put onion bag in lower shelf
Get water filter
Get cup
Fill water
Put water filter
Drink from cup
Put cup down
Pick up lid
Pick up pan
Put pan
Put lid
Pick up pan
Put pan
Pick up lid
Put lid
Pick up pan
Move pan
Put lid
Pick up pan
Put pan
under the next one
Open cupboard
Pick up pot
close cupboard
put pot on stove
pick up chopping board
put chopping board
open fridge
pick up yogurt
put yogurt
pick up broccoli
get scissors
open plastic cover using scissors
remove plastic cover
open trash bin
throw cover
close trash bin
open cap
rinse broccoli
Sprinkle water on broccoli
Close tap
Pick up scissors
Move broccoli and scissors to chopping board
Cut broccoli
Still cutting broccoli
Separate broccoli using hands
Pick up rest of broccoli
Open trash bin
Throw broccoli
Close trash bin
Remove from floor
Open trash bin
Close trash bin
Open tap
Rinse scissors
Close tap
Put scissors down
Open lid
Put lid
Move pan
Move broccoli from chopping board to pan using hands
open tap
fill pan with water
close tap
put pan with broccoli on stove
switch stove on
pick up towel
dry hands
put towel
pick up towel from floor
open fridge
get Tupperware
pick up plate
open Tupperware
put plate
pick up chicken from Tupperware
put chicken on plate
close Tupperware
put Tupperware in sink
pick up knife
pick up scissors
open onion bag
pick up onion
pick up another onion
put onion on chopping board
open trash bin
throw onion
return scissors
pick up knife
chop end of onion
peel onion
Put onion
Pick up chopping board
Open trash bin
Throw peels
Close trash bin
Put chopping board
Put onion on chopping board
Put knife
Pick up kettle
Open kettle
Open tap
Fill kettle
Hold tap and
Close tap
Close kettle
Put kettle down
Switch kettle on
Open cupboard
“pick pot”
“remove lid”
“close cupboard”
“put pot on stove”
“move the other pot”
“pick up lid of pan”
“slice onions”
“still slicing onions”
“chop onions”
“still chopping”
“slices of onion”
“still shopping onion”
still chopping onion
pick up breast of onion slices
open trash bin
throw slices
close trash bin
get paper towel
open trash bin
throw paper towel
close trash bin
open fridge
get pine nuts back
put pine nuts back
open cupboard
get salt
get oil
put oil down
put salt down
open oil
sprinkle oil on pan
pour oil pour oil in pan
close oil
put oil down
switch stove on
put pine nuts in pan
add pine nuts to pan
open fridge
return pine nuts
close fridge
move tray
pick up plate
open microwave
put plate in microwave
close microwave
unplug
move plug
plug into socket
switch microwave on
Move pan
Open draw
Get wooden spoon
Stir pine nuts in pan using wooden spoon
Still stirring pine nuts
Move pan
Hold pan and stir pine nuts
Open cupboard
Get plate
Put plate down
Hold pan and stir pine nuts
Still stirring pine nuts.
Switch stove off
Pick up pan
Slide pine nuts from pan to plate using wooden spoon
Put pan down
Switch of microwave
Open microwave
Open fridge
Searching fridge
Pick up cheese
Pick up pasta
Pick up pesto
Close fridge
Put pesto
Move salt
Move pesto
Put pasta
Put cheese
Switch stove off
Open cupboard
pickup mesh
pickup pot
pour broccoli from pot to mesh
shake mesh
put mesh on plate
move mesh
put mesh onto
put pan
open cupboard
get plate
put mesh onto plate
put plate and mesh down
pickup kettle
pour water
from kettle to pot
still pouring water
put kettle down
read the recipe on pasta
put pasta down
pick up scissors
cut pasta bag
switch stove on
pour pasta into pot
close pasta bag
set timer on
open fridge
put pasta bag in fridge
close fridge
pick up plate from microwave
close microwave
move scissors
put plate
pick up oil
sprinkle oil into pasta pot
pick up salt
put salt into pasta pot
put salt
lower heat on stove
pick up chopping board with onions
chop a few onions using knife
pick up chopping board
switch stove on
move wooden spoon
pick up knife
slide onions from chopping board to pan
put chopping board and knife into sink
pick up knife
stir onions in pan using wooden spoon
divide onion into smaller pieces using wooden spoon
pick up onion piece
put onion piece
stir onion in pan using wooden spoon
Pickup garlic
Put garlic into pan
Close garlic
Put garlic
Stir garlic and onions in pan using wooden spoon
Lower heat
Stir onions using wooden spoon in pan
Pick up knife
Hold chicken piece
Chop chicken piece using knife
Still chopping chicken
Put knife down
Pick up two spoons
Put two spoons
Hold pan
Stir onions in pan using wooden spoon
Increase heat on stove
Pick up two spoons
Open pesto
Scoop pesto using spoon
Put pesto into pan
Close pesto
Put pesto down
Put spoon down
Pick up cheese and
Pick up spoon
Hold cheese and
Scoop cheese using spoon
Put cheese into pan
Scoop more cheese
Put spoon into sink
Put cheese down
Pick up spoon
Move water from pot to pan
lower heat
move water using spoon
from pot to pan
still moving more water
put spoon down
mix cheese pesto and onions in pan using wooden spoon
still mixing cheese and pesto in pan using wooden spoon
still mixing cheese and sauce into pan using wooden spoon
pick up pinenuts(?) plate
pour pine nuts into pan
put plate
pick up plate with chicken
pour chicken into pan using spoon
put plate
.pick up mushroom broccoli
pour broccoli into pan
put mush down
hold pan and mix sauce
stir sauce use wooden spoon
pick up spoon
move water from pot to pan
move water
“put spoon”
“increase heat”
“hold pan” and
“stir sauce”
“increase heat”
“hold pan” and
“stir sauce”
“set a timer”
“still stirring sauce”
“lower heat”
“hold pan” and
“stir sauce”
“open cupboard”
“search in cupboard”
“pick up steel mash”
“close cupboard”
hold stain and stir sauce
set off time
switch off stove
pickup pot with pasta
move chopping board from sink
pour water and pasta from pot to mesh in on top of sink
shake mesh with pasta
pour pasta into pan
put mesh in sink
hold pan and stir pasta with sauce
mix pasta with sauce
still mixing pasta with sauce
using wooden spoon
set off alarm
hold pan
stir pasta with sauce
increase heat
switch off stove
close oil
pickup chopping board
put chopping board
pickup scissors
return scissors
pick up plate
put plate
pick up pan
pour pasta from pan to plate using wooden spoon
still pouring pasta
put pan
put spoon
check stove
pick up plate
open drawer
pick up fork
close drawer
[END SUBTITLE]